[
    {
	    "question": "Pokemon with highest HP stat",
	    "answers": ["Blissey"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is Mega Venusaur's ability",
	    "answers": ["Thick Fat"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "How many PP does hyper beam have normally (number only)",
	    "answers": ["5"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "This is the only Dark-Type move Clawitzer learns.",
	    "answers": ["Dark Pulse"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Which Pokemon according to the Unova horoscope represents Libra?",
	    "answers": ["Lampent"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What Fighting-type move is guaranteed to cause a critical hit?",
	    "answers": ["Storm Throw"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What ability boosts the power of Fire-type moves when the Pokemon is below 1/3 of its health?",
	    "answers": ["Blaze"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is the subtitle of the first Pokémon movie?",
	    "answers": ["Mewtwo Strikes Back"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Name a move that can have a 100% chance of flinching the target barring Fake Out.",
	    "answers": ["Fling"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is the only Poison-Type Pokemon to learn Rock Polish?",
	    "answers": ["Garbodor"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What cave lies between Mahogany Town and Blackthorn City?",
	    "answers": ["Ice Path"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "This Electric-Type move increases the user's Special Defense.",
	    "answers": ["Charge"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is the only Pokémon available in the Yellow Forest Pokéwalker route?",
	    "answers": ["Pikachu"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "This is the nickname of the Pokemon acting as the light source of Glitter Lighthouse in Olivine City.",
	    "answers": ["Amphy"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "This Pokemon has the longest cry.",
	    "answers": ["Jynx"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "This Pokemon Conquest warlord has the warrior ability of \"chesto!\" at rank 2.",
	    "answers": ["Yoshihiro"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What Pokemon is based on the mythological kitsune?",
	    "answers": ["Ninetales"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What Move does HM02 contain?",
	    "answers": ["Fly"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What Pokemon was Latias combined with in early concept art?",
	    "answers": ["Blaziken"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is Prof. Oak's first name?",
	    "answers": ["Samuel"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Who ran the bank in Pokemon Mystery Dungeon: Explorers of Time, Darkness, and Sky?",
	    "answers": ["Duskull"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Which Pseudo legendary was originally based off of a tank?",
	    "answers": ["Hydreigon"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Which Legendary Pokemon was originally found at Victory Road but was moved to the Sevii Islands in later generations?",
	    "answers": ["Moltres"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What Pokemon requires an empty space in the party during evolution to be obtained?",
	    "answers": ["Shedinja"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Which Pokemon has the lowest base stat total?",
	    "answers": ["Sunkern"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "In the main series game, this Pokemon can evolve into its final form using either one of 2 methods.",
	    "answers": ["Feebas"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Which Pokemon Has the Highest \"Attack\" stat that is **Not** A Legendary or Mega",
	    "answers": ["Rampardos"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Which Pokemon Has the Highest \"Speed\" stat that is **Not** A Legendary or Mega",
	    "answers": ["Ninjask"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Which Pokemon Has the Highest \"Defense\" stat that is **Not** A Legendary or Mega",
	    "answers": ["Shuckle"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Which Pokemon Has the Highest \"Special Defense\" stat that is **Not** A Legendary or Mega",
	    "answers": ["Shuckle"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Which Pokemon Has the Highest \"Special Attack\" stat that is **Not** A Legendary or Mega",
	    "answers": ["Chandelure"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Which Pokemon Has the Lowest \"HP\" stat",
	    "answers": ["Shedinja"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "This ability is exclusive to Dragonite and Lugia.",
	    "answers": ["Multiscale"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "This, Servine's hidden ability, is also the hidden ability of Spinda",
	    "answers": ["Contrary"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Water-type starter pokemon have this ability as their primary ability.",
	    "answers": ["Torrent"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Most legendary pokemon have this ability, which doubles the amount of PP opponents use up when attacking.",
	    "answers": ["Pressure"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Pokemon with this ability are immune to moves such as Bug Buzz and Boomburst.",
	    "answers": ["Soundproof"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "This ability allows the pokemon to change typing and appearance when the weather shifts.",
	    "answers": ["Forecast"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "A pokemon's speed stat is doubled in the rain when it has this ability.",
	    "answers": ["Swift Swim"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "This move is the signature move of Chatot.",
	    "answers": ["Chatter"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Aside from smeargle, Lugia is the only pokemon that can learn this flying-type move with an increased critical-hit rate.",
	    "answers": ["Aeroblast"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "This move deals supereffective damage to water-type pokemon even when used by a pokemon with Normalize.",
	    "answers": ["Freeze Dry"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "This move is given as a technical machine after defeating Tate & Liza.",
	    "answers": ["Calm Mind"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "A hidden machine introduced in Diamond and Pearl, this move deals normal-typed damage and may confuse the opponent.",
	    "answers": ["Rock Climb"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "This pokemon is first encountered inside a TV set in the Old Chateau.",
	    "answers": ["Rotom"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "This guaranteed-shiny pokemon can be encountered in the Nature Preserve.",
	    "answers": ["Haxorus"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "This is the only pokemon that can be encountered walking in Rusturf Tunnel.",
	    "answers": ["Whismur"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "As thanks for stopping Team Magma/Aqua, the Weather Institute gives you one of these pokemon.",
	    "answers": ["Castform"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "This pokemon is the only one to have the ability Stance Change.",
	    "answers": ["Aegislash"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "As you liberate Silph Co. from Team Rocket, an employee will give you one of these pokemon.",
	    "answers": ["Lapras"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "This pokemon costs 9999 coins at the Celadon Game Corner.",
	    "answers": ["Porygon"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "You can receive this pokemon as a gift from Bebe.",
	    "answers": ["Eevee"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "This ghost-type evolves from female Snorunt.",
	    "answers": ["Froslass"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "This lake guardian resides in Lake Verity.",
	    "answers": ["Mesprit"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "This person is the Hoenn Champion in Pokemon Emerald.",
	    "answers": ["Wallace"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "The pokemon PC system is operated by this lady in the Hoenn Region.",
	    "answers": ["Lanette"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "The pokemon PC system was expanded to allow trade with Hoenn by this resident of One Island",
	    "answers": ["Celio"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Pokemon Platinum introduced this NPC, a scientist working with Team Galactic that was arrested in Stark Mountain.",
	    "answers": ["Charon"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Viridian's gym leader, he is also the boss of Team Rocket.",
	    "answers": ["Giovanni"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "This person is the head of Team Galactic.",
	    "answers": ["Cyrus"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "This member of the Seven Sages resurrected Team Plasma in the events of Black and White 2.",
	    "answers": ["Ghetsis"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "A member of the Hoenn elite four, this person's team includes Altaria and Flygon.",
	    "answers": ["Drake"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "This item has a 3/16 chance to move the user to the top of its priority bracket.",
	    "answers": ["Quick Claw"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Holders of this item cannot become infatuated, and they also guarantee their offspring inherit 5 stats from its parents.",
	    "answers": ["Destiny Knot"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Defeating the Winstrate family and talking to them afterward allows the player to receive this item, which doubles the EV gains of its holder.",
	    "answers": ["Macho Brace"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "This item is found deep inside Mt. Ember after the player receives the National Pokedex.",
	    "answers": ["Ruby"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Sinnoh's underground can be visited once the player has obtained this Key Item.",
	    "answers": ["Explorer Kit"]
	}
	{
	    "question": "This item summons Heatran when brought to Stark Mountain or Reversal Mountain.",
	    "answers": ["Magma Stone"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What Pokemon is based off of antlion larvae?",
	    "answers": ["Trapinch"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What Pokemon trainer gives you a Dusk Stone in ORAS after defeating them?",	    "answers": ["Hex Maniac Valerie"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What move increases the Attack and Sp. Attack of grounded Grass-type Pokemon?",
	    "answers": ["Rototiller"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Who is the daughter of a gym leader that became a member of the Elite Four?",
	    "answers": ["Janine"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is Ash's first Pokémon?",
	    "answers": ["Pikachu"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Which item evolves Slowbro to Slowking when traded?",
	    "answers": ["King's Rock"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Which Ice-Type move is guaranteed to cause a critical hit?",
	    "answers": ["Frost Breath"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is Heatran's signature move",
	    "answers": ["Magma Storm"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Gyarados was modelled after what legendary sea monster?",
	    "answers": ["Kraken"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Which ability prevents the use of self-destructing moves?",
	    "answers": ["Damp"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Which ability doubles all stat changes?",
	    "answers": ["Simple"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Which ability prevents the user from getting burnt?",
	    "answers": ["Water Veil"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What pokemon controls time?",
	    "answers": ["Dialga"]
	},
	{	    "question": "What pokemon controls space?",
	    "answers": ["Palkia"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Which Pokemon evolution line has no weaknesses due to their abilities?",
	    "answers": ["Eelektross"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What color are Raichu's cheeks?",
	    "answers": ["Yellow"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is the only Pokemon with the typing Normal/Water?",
	    "answers": ["Bibarel"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is the only Pokemon with the typing Normal/Ground?",
	    "answers": ["Diggersby"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is the only Pokemon with the typing Fire/Water?",
	    "answers": ["Volcanion"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is the only Pokemon with the typing Fire/Rock?",
	    "answers": ["Magcargo"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is the only Pokemon with the typing Water/Steel?",
	    "answers": ["Empoleon"]
	},
	
	    "question": "What is the only Pokemon with the typing Electric/Ground?",
	    "answers": ["Stunfisk"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is the only Pokemon with the typing Electric/Fairy?",
	    "answers": ["Dedenne"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is the only Pokemon with the typing Grass/Ground?",
	    "answers": ["Torterra"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is the only Pokemon with the typing Fighting/Flying?",
	    "answers": ["Hawlucha"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is the only Pokemon with the typing Rock/Fighting?",
	    "answers": ["Terrakion"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is the only Pokemon with the typing Poison/Dragon?",
	    "answers": ["Dragalge"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is the only Pokemon with the typing Steel/Flying?",
	    "answers": ["Skarmory"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is the only Pokemon with the typing Psychic/Ghost?",
	    "answers": ["Hoopa"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is the only Pokemon with the typing Bug/Water?",
	    "answers": ["Surskit"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is the only Pokemon with the typing Bug/Ghost?",
	    "answers": ["Shedinja"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is the only Pokemon with the typing Steel/Dragon?",
	    "answers": ["Dialga"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is Liepard's hidden ability?",
	    "answers": ["Prankster"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is Charizard's hidden ability?",
	    "answers": ["Solar Power"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "This ability raises its Pokemon's Speed by 1 at the end of each turn.",
	    "answers": ["Speed Boost"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What type of Pokemon does Drayden mainly use?",
	    "answers": ["Dragon"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "This move randomly does the amount of damage in between 50% and 150% of the user's level.",
	    "answers": ["Psywave"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Using this move raises a Pokemon's Special Attack by 3.",
	    "answers": ["Tail Glow"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "In Dragon's Den you might receive a Dratini knowing what move?",
	    "answers": ["Extreme Speed"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Using this move raises a Pokemon's Defense by 3.",
	    "answers": ["Cotton Guard"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is Pikachu's name in Japanese?",
	    "answers": ["Pikachu"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is the only Pokemon with a BST of 507?",
	    "answers": ["Pyroar"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What Pokemon evolves when it levels up with a Remoraid in the party?",
	    "answers": ["Mantyke"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Seed Flare is the signature move of what Pokemon?",
	    "answers": ["Shaymin"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What Pokemon can learn both Fusion Bolt and Fusion Flare?",
	    "answers": ["Victini"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What move increases Attack and Special Attack by 2 in sun?",
	    "answers": ["Growth"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is Natural Gift's highest possible Base Power?",
	    "answers": ["100"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "As of ORAS, what is the only Pokemon that can Mega Evolve without a Mega Stone?",
	    "answers": ["Rayquaza"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Who is the God of Pokemon?",
	    "answers": ["Arceus"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What ability raises Attack by 2 if one of its stats is lowered?",
	    "answers": ["Defiant"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Most pseudo-legendaries are non-legendaries with what BST?",
	    "answers": ["600"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is the only legendary that can be used to make an egg?",
	    "answers": ["Manaphy"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is the only move that has a 70% chance to raise its user's Special Attack?",
	    "answers": ["Charge Beam"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "In which region would you receive a PokéGear?",
	    "answers": ["Johto"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What was the first region where Pokemon Contests were introduced?",
	    "answers": ["Hoenn"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What ability changes the type of all of a Pokemon's moves to Normal?",
	    "answers": ["Normalize"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What ability heals a poisoned or badly poisoned Pokemon instead of dealing damage?",
	    "answers": ["Poison Heal"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Which item only affects a Farfetch'd?",
	    "answers": ["Stick"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What Pokemon's mega form has the ability Prankster?",
	    "answers": ["Banette"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What Pokemon's mega form has the ability Filter?",
	    "answers": ["Aggron"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What Pokemon gains (not replaces) the Fairy type when it Mega Evolves?",
	    "answers": ["Audino"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What move changes the target's type to Water?",
	    "answers": ["Soak"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Which Pokemon with the highest BST can be affected by the held item Eviolite?",
	    "answers": ["Porygon2"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What item gives its holder a 10% chance to survive an attack that would have fainted it?",
	    "answers": ["Focus Band"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What ability notifies you when any foe has a super effective or OHKO move?",
	    "answers": ["Anticipation"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "In Pokemon Heart Gold and Soul Silver, what level is Red's Pikachu?",
	    "answers": ["88"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What Pokemon has the signature ability Bad Dreams?",
	    "answers": ["Darkrai"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is the only Pokemon with a Zen form?",
	    "answers": ["Darmanitan"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Magikarp evolves at what level?",
	    "answers": ["20"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What single-use item restores a Pokemon's stats if any of them are lowered?",
	    "answers": ["White Herb"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What move raises a Pokemon's attack by 2 if it knocks out its opponent?",
	    "answers": ["Fell Stinger"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What ability raises a Pokemon's Attack by 1.5x but lowers its accuracy by 20%?",
	    "answers": ["Hustle"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What Fire-type move does more damage the heavier the user is than the target?",
	    "answers": ["Heat Crash"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Who is the female counterpart to Red in Pokemon Fire Red and Leaf Green?",
	    "answers": ["Leaf"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is the biggest Pokemon by height?",
	    "answers": ["Wailord"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is the fastest Pokemon **including** legendaries?",
	    "answers": ["Deoxys-speed"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What Pokemon got banned from Ubers?",
	    "answers": ["Mega Rayquaza", "Rayquaza-mega"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is the Fresh Snow Pokemon that evolves from Eevee?",
	    "answers": ["Glaceon"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What Pokemon has the most evolutions?",
	    "answers": ["Eevee"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What **Fighting Type** Pokemon has the most evolutions?",
	    "answers": ["Tyrogue"]
	},	{
	    "question": "I want to be the best Pokemon master ever. Who am I?",
	    "answers": ["Ash"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is the only Pokemon to have a number in their name?",
	    "answers": ["Porygon2"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Name one of Ash's female travel companions",
	    "answers": ["Misty", "Dawn", "May", "Iris", "Bonnie", "Serena"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "These Pokemon have 600BST evenly distributed across the stats.",
	    "answers": ["Mew", "Celebi", "Jirachi", "Shaymin", "Manaphy", "Victini"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Name one of the 3 starters in the Unova Region.",
	    "answers": ["Snivy", "Oshawott", "Tepig"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Name one of Hoenn's Psychic type gym leaders",
	    "answers": ["Tate", "Liza"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Name a Pokemon that has a BST of 590",
	    "answers": ["Altaria-mega", "Kangaskhan-mega", "Slowbro-Mega", "Mega Altaria", "Mega Kangaskhan", "Mega Slowbro"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "And his name is.....",
	    "answers": ["John Cena!"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "This is the only thing to learn chatter besides chatot.",
	    "answers": ["F-00"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "There are this many item plates.",
	    "answers": ["17"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Name a pokemon that has a . in it's name.",
	    "answers": ["Mr. Mime", "Mime Jr.", "Missingno."]
	},
	{
	    "question": "This is the only pokemon that has a ' in it's name.",
	    "answers": ["Farfetch'd"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "This is the only move with a number in it's name",
	    "answers": ["Conversion2"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is Eusine's trainer class in Crystal?",
	    "answers": ["Mystery Man"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is the only Pokémon that is weak to both of its types?",
	    "answers": ["Giratina", "Giratina-Origin", "Giratina-O"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Mantine is the counterpart to which Pokémon?",
	    "answers": ["Skarmory"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is Volkner's signature Pokémon in the DPP games?",
	    "answers": ["Electivire"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Who is the only in-game Champion to have perfect IV Pokémon?",
	    "answers": ["Cynthia"
	},
	{
	    "question": "Who is the Bolt Strike Pokémon?",
	    "answers": ["Thundurus"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Name an Gen6 OU Pokémon with 110 base speed",
	    "answers": ["Diancie-mega", "Gengar", "Latios", "Latias", "Metagross-mega"]
	},
	
	    "question": "What is the only fully evolved starter WITHOUT a base stat divisible by 5?",
	    "answers": ["Infernape"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Name a Mega with a weather-inducing ability.",
	    "answers": ["Charizard-Mega Y", "Abomasnow-mega", "Tyranitar-Mega", "Mega Charizard Y", "Mega Abomasnow", "Mega Tyranitar"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Name a non-Mega Pokémon in BL.",
	    "answers": ["Crawdaunt", "Diggersby", "Hawlucha", "Scolipede", "Staraptor", "Terrakion", "Togekiss", "Victini", "Volcarona", "Zygarde"
	},
	{
	    "question": "Name a starter that is banned from OU?",
	    "answers": ["Blaziken", "Greninja"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Prior to the release of HG/SS, which trainer had the strongest in-game team?",
	    "answers": ["Barry"]
	},
	
	    "question": "Using this move raises Special Attack, Special Defense and Speed by 1 stage.",
	    "answers": ["Quiver Dance"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "In the battle with Cyrus in the Distortion World in Pokémon Platinum, all of his Pokémon had a shared weakness to what type?",
	    "answers": ["Rock"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What was the subtitle for the 10th Pokémon movie?",
	    "answers": ["The Rise of Darkrai"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What was the subtitle for the 14th Pokémon movie?",
	    "answers": ["White: Victini and Reshiram", "Black: Victini and Zekrom"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What was the first fourth generation Pokémon to be revealed in the anime?",
	    "answers": ["Electivire"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "Which berry healed a Pokémon by 30 HP in Generation 3?",
	    "answers": ["Sitrus"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is the signature move of the Mahukita evolutionary line?",
	    "answers": ["Smelling Salts"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is the signature move of Hoopa-Confined?",
	    "answers": ["Hyperspace Hole"]
	},
	{
	    "question": "What is the only poison type with 420 BST",
	    "answers": ["Qwilfish"]
	},  
        {
	    "question": "My Owner!"
	    "answers": ["A Flying Phantom"]
	} 
        {
	    "question":"Name one of the owners of Cerberus Server" 
	    "answers":["A Flying Phantom", "Giovanni The Best"]
]
